so our first project in the global
cooperative is going to be one that
creates community and conversation and
from that base we're able to do all of
the dozens and hundreds and infinite
number of projects that are going to
give us all of the resources and all of
the community and all of the information
we need to create massive change very
rapidly on this planet but it starts
with one project and our first project
is the idea cafe we are going to create
our own social media platform that is
designed for a meaningful conversation
with a large group of people on existing
social media platform like Twitter I
hear constantly like these people went
off on this person you look and it's 12
people who went off on them and it's
very divisive and there's a lot of
debate in online none of is designed for
an actual conversation none of it is
designed to understand the other
person's side that if it's designed to
actually come to a understanding and
move forward together on things they're
gonna benefit us all so we are going to
create that what it's going to be
modeled after is a World Cafe format a
World Cafe is an in-person way to have a
conversation with a large group of
people it's been done in Fortune 500
companies and nonprofits and unions
where you get together hundreds of
people and they meet in groups of four
or five around a more intimate cafe
style table they're able to draw their
ideas they're able to everyone around
the table was invited to share and they
have a conversation around a meaningful
question then everybody gets up from
that table and they disperse and talk to
new people about that same meaningful
question so in that way the larger group
is able to have a conversation because
you're also then harvesting those
conversations and asking what are the
threads we found throughout what was
talked about at every different table
what was the uniqueness what was the
commonality and so we are going to host
the idea cafe on existing technology
while we work out the kinks and figure
out how many people we want to I don't
even want to be involved
how do we make this so that people want
to be involved so that it's fun so that
it's simple for people because that is
how we get the masses involved and we
want the masses involved we want their
energy we want their their intelligence
we want anyone who wants to be part of
creating a better world to be invited to
be part of creating a better world and
so the idea Cafe is on its way I'm
figuring out every iteration that we
need to get to you to get to there but
the current iteration is that we are
going to have a weekly timeslot or I am
gonna meet on camera with three other
people and we're gonna host that
intimate conversation not the bigger one
with hundreds of people but that one
around one one table and the question is
either gonna be generated by me
generated by other people who want to be
part of that conversation and those
people might rotate every week and they
might end up being the same people it
depends on who is interested and who
wants to continually be on camera having
a conversation about a meaningful
question once we have people involved
you guys can can submit what questions
you want us to talk about and you can
talk about them because as soon as
there's enough people who want to get
involved it can't fit on that camera or
just aren't interested in being on
camera for everyone I hope you subscribe
hopefully there's more to see
we'll be on it we will host an actual
idea Cafe on Zoom oh they'll be a
hundred of us breaking off into tables
of four and once we figure out that
enough time slots we are meeting the
threshold of users of time of all the
stuff that's in my brain that I'm not
able to communicate the same in this
moment what I'm looking for are people
who want to collaborate talk online
about a meaningful question every week
and by every becoming I'm going to be
talking at the same time every week at
that same time period I want to pick a
time period that works for me that is
most conducive to most people so we can
have viewers but more importantly so the
people who want to be on video will be
on video the people don't have to commit
to being on video every week we just
need enough people that it we can
consistently have at least two
preferably three other people on camera
with me
having that conversation about a
meaningful question and so that is the
idea Cafe please like and subscribe and
hit that little Bell a better world is
on its way it's gonna be brought to you
by all of us and our inherent diversity
I can't wait see you tomorrow